my name is Billy Eilish Billy Eilish
I think it's October 18th 2017 its
October eighteenth two thousand eighteen
I'm 15 I'm 16 I have 257,000 I have 6.3
million followers 1.1 3 million nine
point six million when you look up Billy
Eilish it's a picture of me and Charli
XCX it's not the one about me smiling
course it is the one picture that I have
smiling the most followed person that
follows me he's chloë grace moretz who's
the best she has 13 million followers
Katy Perry maybe she is 72 million I'd
say probably Khalid
which is weird cuz he's like just a
homie of mine and like I don't think
women's anything else scissor I have
Millie Bobeck Brown Sabrina Claudia that
baby you're in her regular Osiris Whaley
which the kids and yadi
a girl baby red Miguel are you kidding
me these are people that I've texted it
was at the crocodile in Seattle and it
was like five hundred I think
that's what I said whoa that's so cute
who that was ah the best one I've had
was music Midtown in Atlanta 40,000
people it's such a dream oh my god such
a dream every time I go anywhere hands
down I might be safe if I go to Trader
Joe's but everywhere else is kind of you
recognized which is actually really cool
but it you know it's a lot kind of a lot
actually
but like not a ton it's kind of like
maybe like once a week um I'm kind of
jealous of Billy a year ago because I
kind of I don't know I'm really not
about that pity myself for
people recognizing Who I am which is
because it's like I'm really grateful
for it but I don't know I would like to
go to I don't know anywhere and not be
always recognized whoa oh don't be so
sad it's such a waste of time ah I
didn't I didn't live up to that then and
I still haven't lived up to that so it's
good advice though it is a waste of time
dude
ah it's ruined so many things that could
have been amazing because I was sad dumb
but whatever don't post everything you
think
don't just if you're watching this right
now anybody if anybody is watching this
don't post your feelings don't do it to
yourself
[Music]
whoa Tyler the Creator no I would love
to me uh I'm not many oh my god I would
explode if I met him I met him I met him
and it was great for me he hits a he
hits a part of me that nobody gets being
apples up next artist I was such a baby
I did Ellen last week Jimmy Fallon
Lollapalooza
so many festivals I went to Tokyo I met
Takashi Murakami I went to his studio
Dave girl's daughter did a cover of my
song he played guitar for her in a
talent show I think or something there's
been a lot of that's happened in
the last year my family I'm I'm always
talking to my family always every second
in my life Fruitvale station a Fruitvale
station no you know what no this I can't
afford a real change they are real now
they are real but it's all silver oh
yeah my chains were gifts I did not buy
anything that I'm wearing at all none of
it
I bought this though
ah yes yeah yep
yeah it's the kind of pressure that's
like it hits me and then I don't care
everybody dropped dead right now and I
didn't I would be left with what I had
created for myself and what the hell
would the point be if I was just
creating something that somebody else
wanted me to create that I had no say in
and then that person died and everybody
else died and nobody mattered except me
I'm stuck with this I didn't want
the first place that's a trash no I'm
handling the pressure horribly but I
just keep it to myself all the time
except my wall I write everything I felt
my walls I'd be gone my room my wall
[Music]
just ya know I don't like dating at all
I don't like the idea of oh this is my
one person and I only share the time
with this person no no no no thank you
no I don't have a boyfriend I can't I
could not have a boyfriend that would
just be mean to him I don't know I
almost had one for like a little but it
wasn't really exclusive so I don't know
what you'd call that I hate things that
are exclusive letting myself be
mistreated for a long long long long
time I had no idea what the was
coming not really uh yeah I was really
mistreated treated and then I just
realized I was better than that and
since then I just I feel like I've just
grown to know my worth I think it's
taken a minute and I don't think I'm
there yet but I'm getting there
Oh Billy was so hurt then I was so hurt
then man I want to learn that it's
all worth it because it's tiring as heck
and
it is worth it and I have to remember
that because being with like fans are
doing shows is way more important than
being tired is it worth it yes the shows
make it worth it the shows and the
supporters that is something you have to
remember when it it doesn't feel worth
it because a lot of it doesn't feel
worth it
but then you get to the points that do
make it worth it and it's like then it
all sort of makes sense and it kind of
clicks in your head no matter what you
do there's you can never ever ever
please anyone ever ever ever that's
still true never not true
any picture that is taken of you if a
picture is taken of you somebody has it
and somebody will use it against you
I wasn't allowed to but I ran away from
security and I ran into a huge crowd
I like slammed open a door into all of
them through a glass window and hugged
them all
I almost caused a stampede by sneaking
through a crowd at Lollapalooza I almost
died and everyone else almost died
crazy whoa Lil Wayne I ought to
perform with Lil Wayne that's a great
answer
Wow 15-year old me was ballin I really
want to go to Japan again I went to
Japan a while ago and it was the most
amazing time so I feel like Brazil might
be crazy literally my first fan account
was like or like second Finnick I was
like Billie Islands Brazil Brockhampton
tierra wack is sick I like bright green
a lot I don't like black it's been
pretty dark lately so I've just wanted
to be dark with it the world I mean I
[Music]
don't and then one word no
judge me please that's what I said
I still feel that way totally still feel
that way but this year I guess I just
don't you know I don't know what
is going on I feel this and that I
feel like everything needs to have a
certain this is in this category and
this is in this like it's like I want to
be everything like shut up don't tell me
what I can't be the hell
the music industry man we're all sad as
hell all these artists we're sad as
dude everybody I know that's an artist
we are sad mother it's the way
it is no what does that even mean what
does that mean everyone is gonna die and
no one is gonna remember you so in
with this bitch then that's my fault
filosophy having the approach that no
one's had trying to write something no
one's written I don't know if that's the
best approach because you might just
fail and then want to die like I have to
write someone write something no one's
ever heard see that's why I'm still bad
at it yes that's what I was trying to do
whoo you better know how to drive
because I've been putting enough drivers
in it because that stuff stinks I hate
that stuff I do know how to drive shorty
well that is crazy
this is my mom she is sick as a booty
and she has laryngitis
[Music]
[Applause]