Hello, I'm Bob Ross. And I'd like to welcome you.
First of all, let me take a moment just to thank you for allowing me back into your homes.
If this is your first time with us, let me extend a personal invitation
For you to drag out your oil paints and paint along with us each week.
Let's go to the canvas over week here and get started.
I believe, I believe
Every day is a good day when you paint.
It'll bring a lot of good thoughts to your heart
I believe, I believe, every day's a good when you paint
I believe, I believe, It'll bring a lot of good thoughts to your heart
Let's build a happy little cloud; let's build some happy little trees
There are no limits here
Start out by believing here
you can almost paint with anything
all you have to do is practice
There are no limits here
Start out by believing here
This is your world, you're the creator; find freedom on this canvas
Believe that you can do it, because you can do it.
Give it a little touch, give it a little push; make love to the canvas.
Give it a little touch, give it a little push; caress it, very gentle.
Grab it, lift it, fluff it; you can go on and on and on
back and forth, layer after layer
Let's build a happy little cloud; let's build some happy little trees
There are no limits here. Start out by believing here.
This is your world, you're the creator; find freedom on this canvas
Believe that you can do it, because you can do it.
Relax, let it flow, think like water
Relax, let it flow, you can go on and on and on
We don't make mistakes; just happy accidents.
You can do anything that you want to do, total power.
Sing along, have a good time:
Do do do
This is your world, you're the creator; find freedom on this canvas
Believe that you can do it, because you can do it.
I believe, I believe, that every day's a good day when you paint
I believe, I believe it'll bring a lot of good thoughts to your heart
I believe, I believe every day's a good day when you paint