hey guys welcome back to being a 32 year
old lady Oh
so after the last time that I painted
when I followed a Bob Ross tutorial I
realized how much I genuinely enjoy
painting I also realized that oil paint
is not the paint for me it got literally
everywhere including permit and a lot of
you suggested that I keep trying with
different types of paint one of which
was acrylic paint also some of my
favorite YouTube videos to watch some of
the most relaxing content on this
website is acrylic pork videos basically
take acrylic paint and like dump it onto
a thing and that's your paint which
sounds like the kind of painting that
I'd be good at because I can't really
draw or paint or think in general so I
need something a little more freeform
Julian's here because he's so jealous of
when I painted Bob Ross he wanted to
join the law just don't make a mess I
mean you're gonna make a mess but like
don't make an Aries mess we literally
bought like sheets of vinyl from the
fabric store which I didn't know you
could do but we covered the table and
the floor but like the mess needs to
stay here it can't go like in this kind
of direction like an Aries no not that
direction the whole kitchen is not on
limits so I watched a bunch of acrylic
poor beginner videos and basically when
it comes down to is you need acrylic
paint and some type of thinning medium
there's people that use like glue and
water and liquid silicone and dish soap
and all kinds of stuff what I found is
that this is like just a ready-made
thing that we can do because I don't
know what I'm doing and you're supposed
to put them in cups but the girl at the
art store said that this might be even
better
if you mix it in a thing and then you
can pour it this way instead of dumping
all these open cups I don't know we'll
see what happens so you mix half color
half we don't know there's all different
kinds of ratios some of them are like
1/3 of this and 2/3 of that or vice
versa did you just eat that what colors
are you gonna do
because I'm gonna do all bread I
realized like as an adult the things
that I get excited about like actually
excited about are all like arts and
crafts because they spent all my life
like
doing my academic studies and sports
this part of my life never got explored
and I feel like it's just coming out of
me as a 32 year old lady how beautifully
put it seems so much more like clean and
not messy because at this table was full
of cups of colors right now one of us
would be able to make sure that none of
them got dumped over the other one is
Julian there's basically no ropes like
you just do whatever you want but
there's clean pores which is where you
sort of pour them in a pattern or like
in a circle and then there's dirty pores
where you take a cup you ready and you
pour it all in the cup and then you pour
the cup out oh I'm really excited for
that like I'm already having such a good
time this is fun
you don't really do acrylic pores on the
leg of canvas I guess cuz it'll like
melt down cuz it's a lot of weight it's
a lot of paint so we're using these what
do they call their like black sort of
boards we why we have two yellows
because they've got a really bright
yellow for me to use and you can use the
normal average looking yellow okay
that's not fair the only thing about
acrylic pores is it it looks like you
just waste a fucked on a paint but like
it's for art so I guess you could
measure these if you really felt like it
but even my Burgo ass doesn't feel like
measuring anything people on YouTube
will put like a strainer down and then
pour it through the strainer like the
possibilities I fucking endless each and
the hours of watch time I fucking
endless I've arranged them all in
rainbow order or else we can't do it you
want to start with a clean bore clean
pool yeah cuz that's like the basic I've
never done it before so underneath here
we have like you could put anything but
we just cut like a little piece of foam
so that this can dry because it needs to
drip off the sides
I'm really scared but excited because I
know that there's no rules but I also am
overwhelmed by choices I'm gonna start
okay I'm scared is it coming out slow
you could just go like this
so mmm there's so many bubbles what's
what are you doing my inspiration is
the colors blue and I think I made some
of these way too watery oh it's
beautiful be yours looks like of the
good consistency and mine's just like
full of bubbles and shit
whoa yours is really going for it
oh shit Oh yours this like really bold
and wild when do I start doing it
whenever you can do whatever you want
alright well here we go whoa Oh careful
Oh oh I love it
oh it's beautiful that's really great
nice I turned out really bad I'm yeah
better to hubli in no it's really good
why did you call it bad looks weird keep
going it looks really nice looking well
okay those are all the cells that's like
if you let it just sort of like chill
it'll start moving and doing its own
thing but you don't even have to pay
it's painting for you it's painting for
me oh I love it oh oh he's an Aries oh
that's so dope whoa oh I really like it
I admire your boldness and your
decisiveness I don't have that what is
that
oh dude fucking artist so good looks
like an egg I hate it okay it's already
pouring off oh no did I ruin it
am i ruining it did I ruin it I'm gonna
do mine you ready yeah do it will you
fight yeah oh my god finally a kind of
painting that I can do it's really
relaxing
I love yours Juliet what happens a
virgin you can do whatever you want
oh wait no no I don't think that's an
acrylic floor anymore
oh my name oh my god no
my name is underneath I know there's no
rules but I think you right oh cool you
writing your name under something and
then just going over it is not exactly
what it's meant to be but I mean do you
so I will say that putting them in the
bottles does give you a lot of air
bubbles but I don't know if that's like
helping the cells or if it's like making
them worse or better I'm not sure
aving fine having so much fun talking
why are you covered in pain so I guess
as you like do more of these you
probably get a lot better
this technique huh cuz they both started
just like dumped it out whoa yours keeps
literally changing yeah they're
constantly in flux
my first acrylic part huh do you like it
I like it a lot do you like mine yeah I
love yours may be different see I love
that what you just dripped off of your
painting onto here yeah like I think
this lifts up your thing I feel like
your tray came out so cool yeah what if
we do that since there's no rules can I
dump my tray onto it it's so fun please
don't tell me in the comments that I
ruined my acrylic or by doing this
because I made it great this is like a
meta acrylic or I think it's so cool
whoa yours looks fucking crazy yeah it
turned out crazy when you have those
extra colors you need no skills though
which is what I need I need just a pure
form of creativity without any special
skills required well I will say that
neither of ours really came out like an
acrylic core with like the concentric
circles or whatever but like I'm not mad
fuckin I love that I love tattoos like
the longer it sits here the more it like
changes yeah changing it's really hard
to know when to stop I I don't want to
stop it doesn't really look like any of
the ones
do on YouTube don't have a hard time
following directions oh I really like
your choices three layers under that
says did you make gloves off I want to
set this somewhere let it dry and then
we're gonna do a dirty pour which is
when you pour all of the paint into a
cup and then pour it on top and whatever
it is that it it shouldn't be a dirty
pour it it's a destiny pour you like it
cuz you don't have to make a decision
yes you pour all the pain here and then
you drink it there's a hurry I think I'm
gonna use like not a million colors
I'm swirling it when it's in here yeah
this is dog oh this is so cool this is
gonna be fun is this enough for anymore
I don't know are you ready for this I'm
ready what you're gonna do
remove your styrofoam really quick try
take it put on top of your cup and then
flip it I think you just like pick it up
and do whatever and then you move it
around yeah - one whip Oh fine - looks
like wallpaper I like I absolutely love
doing this it's just as fun as watching
a video but like it's just my fingers
are so many touch - relaxing - watch
this isn't it my fingers touched right
here it's fine babe just keep going this
is no longer a dirty porn it's
officially a clean four again I wish
that I had like a little more like
payoff you know what it means my two
friends play no don't say that
don't drip your painting on my painting
all right I changed my mind my sponge is
actually my canvas that's so fun yeah
stuff dripping your painting oh no my
painting this is more fun arguably than
finger-painting why don't you show them
what you're doing it's a representation
of my journey use all the tools at your
disposal that's what the Fisher man with
a gun said I call this one hell escape
well here's the thing is that this was
really fun but I can't tell if I like
this or not like the final result yeah I
know there was like a bunch of
renditions that happen and halfway
through that I like so you don't keep
acrylic paintings you throw them out you
burn them what Hirai I don't think that
I like this I definitely hate mine I
like yours I think yours looks cool I
don't really like it is that like what
art is like how are you supposed to just
fucking stop I'm gonna discard this in a
very violent way but I'm gonna remember
this journey no I think the hardest part
about a car like pouring that they don't
show you on YouTube is just how
difficult it is to stop I like actually
genuinely loved yours don't you it's not
bright colors mine has no bright colors
I hate it I want mine to be yours so
this was my first acrylic pour ever I
think it's pretty cool it's like
changing it's swirling it's doing cool
stuff
I don't know has a lot of movement in
color which I am enjoying here's
Julian's
acrylic or different than mine but like
really cool actually like this the
longer it's at there yeah cuz they're
like changes and settles here's the
result of your dirty poor most of which
ended up on the table house key as much
as your troll I genuinely like he'll
escape and I want to hang that up in the
house sweet and then here is my
originally a dirty poor which turned
into something that I absolutely cannot
stand no it's good it looks like a
post-apocalyptic world and the sky is
still shining blue then there's this
fiery pit of death and despair over here
which is from the apocalypse but it
still looks beautiful and that's the new
Sun I wish it didn't exist
either way though like this was so fun
this was like this is a style of
painting that I feel like is really
cathartic and like really fun and really
nice and I enjoyed making it as much as
I enjoy watching the videos which I feel
like doesn't really happen be done it
looks like a piece of shit are you glad
that you got to do this this would be
fun I do drunk yeah like let's have a
Saturday night or we just drink wine and
acrylic pour live stream on Twitch I
hope you don't mind us doing something a
little different doing something
together because I really wanted to try
it now I know what it feels like it
feels terrible but like I'll feel great
at the same time is that what art is
just in general like terrible but like
great it's a roller coaster of highs and
lows the high of doing it and the low of
looking at it
anyways thanks for tuning it into being
a 32 year old lady I'll see you guys
next week bye